<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Emergency Helper</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="using_our_services_you_must_follow_any_policies_made_available_to_you_within_the_services_don_t_misuse_our_services_for_example_don_t_interfere_with_our_services_or_try_to_access_them_using_a_method_other_than_the_interface_and_the_instructions_that_we_provide_you_may_use_our_services_only_as_permitted_by_law_we_may_suspend_or_stop_providing_our_services_to_you_if_you_do_not_comply_with_our_terms_or_policies_or_if_we_are_investigating_suspected_misconduct_using_our_services_does_not_give_you_ownership_of_any_intellectual_property_rights_in_our_services_or_the_content_you_access_you_may_not_use_content_from_our_services_unless_you_obtain_permission_from_its_owner_or_are_otherwise_permitted_by_law_these_terms_do_not_grant_you_the_right_to_use_any_branding_or_logos_used_in_our_services_don_t_remove_obscure_or_alter_any_legal_notices_displayed_in_or_along_with_our_services_our_services_display_some_content_that_is_not_emergency_helper_s_this_content_is_the_sole_responsibility_of_the_entity_that_makes_it_available_we_may_review_content_to_determine_whether_it_is_illegal_or_violates_our_policies_and_we_may_remove_or_refuse_to_display_content_that_we_reasonably_believe_violates_our_policies_or_the_law_but_that_does_not_necessarily_mean_that_we_review_content_so_please_don_t_assume_that_we_do_in_connection_with_your_use_of_the_services_we_may_send_you_service_announcements_administrative_messages_and_other_information_you_may_opt_out_of_some_of_those_communications_some_of_our_services_are_available_on_mobile_devices_do_not_use_such_services_in_a_way_that_distracts_you_and_prevents_you_from_obeying_traffic_or_safety_laws_your_emergency_helper_account_you_need_an_emergency_helper_account_in_order_to_use_our_services_you_may_create_your_own_emergency_helper_account_such_as_your_employer_or_educational_institution_if_you_are_using_a_emergency_helper_account_assigned_to_you_by_an_administrator_different_or_additional_terms_may_apply_and_your_administrator_may_be_able_to_access_or_disable_your_account_to_protect_your_emergency_helper_account_keep_your_password_confidential_you_are_responsible_for_the_activity_that_happens_on_or_through_your_emergency_helper_account_try_not_to_reuse_your_emergency_helper_account_password_on_third_party_applications_if_you_learn_of_any_unauthorized_use_of_your_password_or_emergency_helper_account_follow_these_instructions_privacy_and_copyright_protection_emergency_helper_s_privacy_policies_explain_how_we_treat_your_personal_data_and_protect_your_privacy_when_you_use_our_services_by_using_our_services_you_agree_that_emergency_helper_can_use_such_data_in_accordance_with_our_privacy_policies_we_respond_to_notices_of_alleged_copyright_infringement_and_terminate_accounts_of_repeat_infringers_according_to_the_process_set_out_in_the_philippine_republic_act_no_8293_modifying_and_terminating_our_services_we_are_constantly_changing_and_improving_our_services_we_may_add_or_remove_functionalities_or_features_and_we_may_suspend_or_stop_a_service_altogether_you_can_stop_using_our_services_at_any_time_although_we_ll_be_sorry_to_see_you_go_emergency_helper_may_also_stop_providing_services_to_you_or_add_or_create_new_limits_to_our_services_at_any_time_we_believe_that_you_own_your_data_and_preserving_your_access_to_such_data_is_important_if_we_discontinue_a_service_where_reasonably_possible_we_will_give_you_reasonable_advance_notice_and_a_chance_to_get_information_out_of_that_service_business_uses_of_our_services_if_you_are_using_our_services_on_behalf_of_a_business_that_business_accepts_these_terms_it_will_hold_harmless_and_indemnify_emergency_helper_and_its_affiliates_officers_agents_and_employees_from_any_claim_suit_or_action_arising_from_or_related_to_the_use_of_the_services_or_violation_of_these_terms_including_any_liability_or_expense_arising_from_claims_losses_damages_suits_judgments_litigation_costs_and_attorneys_fees_about_these_terms_we_may_modify_these_terms_or_any_additional_terms_that_apply_to_a_service_to_for_example_reflect_changes_to_the_law_or_changes_to_our_services_you_should_look_at_the_terms_regularly_we_ll_post_notice_of_modifications_to_these_terms_on_this_page_we_ll_post_notice_of_modified_additional_terms_in_the_applicable_service_changes_will_not_apply_retroactively_and_will_become_effective_no_sooner_than_fourteen_days_after_they_are_posted_however_changes_addressing_new_functions_for_a_service_or_changes_made_for_legal_reasons_will_be_effective_immediately_if_you_do_not_agree_to_the_modified_terms_for_a_service_you_should_discontinue_your_use_of_that_service_if_there_is_a_conflict_between_these_terms_and_the_additional_terms_the_additional_terms_will_control_for_that_conflict_these_terms_control_the_relationship_between_emergency_helper_and_you_they_do_not_create_any_third_party_beneficiary_rights_if_you_do_not_comply_with_these_terms_and_we_don_t_take_action_right_away_this_doesn_t_mean_that_we_are_giving_up_any_rights_that_we_may_have_such_as_taking_action_in_the_future_if_it_turns_out_that_a_particular_term_is_not_enforceable_this_will_not_affect_any_other_terms_for_information_about_how_to_contact_emergency_helper_please_visit_our_contact_page">Using our Services You must follow any policies made available to you within the Services. Don’t misuse our Services. For example, don’t interfere with our Services or try to access them using a method other than the interface and the instructions that we provide. You may use our Services only as permitted by law. We may suspend or stop providing our Services to you if you do not comply with our terms or policies or if we are investigating suspected misconduct. Using our Services does not give you ownership of any intellectual property rights in our Services or the content you access. You may not use content from our Services unless you obtain permission from its owner or are otherwise permitted by law. These terms do not grant you the right to use any branding or logos used in our Services. Don’t remove, obscure, or alter any legal notices displayed in or along with our Services. Our Services display some content that is not EMERGENCY HELPER’s. This content is the sole responsibility of the entity that makes it available. We may review content to determine whether it is illegal or violates our policies, and we may remove or refuse to display content that we reasonably believe violates our policies or the law. But that does not necessarily mean that we review content, so please don’t assume that we do. In connection with your use of the Services, we may send you service announcements, administrative messages, and other information. You may opt out of some of those communications. Some of our Services are available on mobile devices. Do not use such Services in a way that distracts you and prevents you from obeying traffic or safety laws. Your EMERGENCY HELPER Account You need an Emergency Helper Account in order to use our Services. You may create your own Emergency Helper Account, such as your employer or educational institution. If you are using a Emergency Helper Account assigned to you by an administrator, different or additional terms may apply and your administrator may be able to access or disable your account. To protect your Emergency Helper Account, keep your password confidential. You are responsible for the activity that happens on or through your Emergency Helper Account. Try not to reuse your Emergency Helper Account password on third-party applications. If you learn of any unauthorized use of your password or Emergency Helper Account, follow these instructions. Privacy and Copyright Protection Emergency Helper’s privacy policies explain how we treat your personal data and protect your privacy when you use our Services. By using our Services, you agree that Emergency Helper can use such data in accordance with our privacy policies. We respond to notices of alleged copyright infringement and terminate accounts of repeat infringers according to the process set out in the Philippine Republic Act No. 8293 Modifying and Terminating our Services We are constantly changing and improving our Services. We may add or remove functionalities or features, and we may suspend or stop a Service altogether. You can stop using our Services at any time, although we’ll be sorry to see you go. Emergency Helper may also stop providing Services to you, or add or create new limits to our Services at any time. We believe that you own your data and preserving your access to such data is important. If we discontinue a Service, where reasonably possible, we will give you reasonable advance notice and a chance to get information out of that Service. Business uses of our Services If you are using our Services on behalf of a business, that business accepts these terms. It will hold harmless and indemnify Emergency Helper and its affiliates, officers, agents, and employees from any claim, suit or action arising from or related to the use of the Services or violation of these terms, including any liability or expense arising from claims, losses, damages, suits, judgments, litigation costs and attorneys’ fees. About these Terms We may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a Service to, for example, reflect changes to the law or changes to our Services. You should look at the terms regularly. We’ll post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. We’ll post notice of modified additional terms in the applicable Service. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen days after they are posted. However, changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for a Service, you should discontinue your use of that Service. If there is a conflict between these terms and the additional terms, the additional terms will control for that conflict. These terms control the relationship between Emergency Helper and you. They do not create any third party beneficiary rights. If you do not comply with these terms, and we don’t take action right away, this doesn’t mean that we are giving up any rights that we may have (such as taking action in the future). If it turns out that a particular term is not enforceable, this will not affect any other terms. For information about how to contact Emergency Helper, please visit our contact page.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
</resources>
